Contact

mohanarao.chakka@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mr-chakka-mohanarao-3b0010157 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Computer Vision machine learning python

Languages

python (Professional Working)Open Cv (Professional Working)c (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards

gold medal

Publications

International journal on" Cellular voting system using Arduino" of Mantech publication April 5th, 2018, India.

International journal on "Voce control-based Home appliances Using Arduino Devices" of IEEE, Jan, 2017, India.

International journal on "Finger print Door locking system using Raspberry pi kit" of IJIRSE April,2017,India.

International journal on "Automated water Plant watering system using Arduino"

nternational journal on "Persistence of vision using Arduino" of Mantech publication Jan ,2014, India

MR Chakka mohanarao

Computer Vision Engineer at Lumirack Solutions Chennai

Summary

Master of Technology in EMBEDDED SYSTEMS and a seasoned professional with 3+ years of experience in the challenging field of the image processing, video survelliance algorithms with computer vision. I carry the practical experience in the domains like:

Computer vision end to end product development image processing,

Video Analytics and Security Surveillance Systems solutions IOT(internet of things)

Visual inspection systems.

Familiar with platforms like Open CV, MATLABScilab, C/C++, Python

Nowadays gearing up with Machine and Deep learning algorithms and CUDA.

Ultimate goal is to instill myself with principles of productive research, efficient time and project management, multi-tasking with efficacy, business development and client relationship.

Experience

Lumirack Solutions
Computer Vision Engineer
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Xvidia Technologies

1 year 11 months

Al Scientist in Computer Vision Product development September 2018 - July 2020 (1 year 11 months)

3+ years professional experience in the software computer vision product development and solving complex prolems in the area image processing with innovative techniques using machine learning and deep learning architectures

AI SCIENTIST

September 2018 - July 2020 (1 year 11 months)

sri tech solutions
Project Consultant
April 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 4 months)
Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh

have been developed lots of real time projects based on digital cameras and IOT based projects using arduino,Raspberry,Computer vision

Sri Sivani College of Engineering, Chilakapalem Junction, Etcherla Mandal, PIN-532402 (CC-W6)
Asst Professor
June 2012 - March 2017 (4 years 10 months)
Srikakulam Area, India

5 years Research and teaching Experience as a expertise in exclusively image processing area Asst. Prof. in Sri Sivani College of Engineering, Affiliated JNTUK. Have done number of projects based on MATLAB, Python, embedded C.

Areas of working:

- 1.Image processing
- 2.Embedded systems
- 3.Bio medical field

Education

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Kakinada Master's degree, EMBEDDED SYSTEMS · (2012 - 2014)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Kakinada B.TECH, electronics instrumentation engineering (2006 - 2010)